(Bernadette:)Okay, movie night--
what do you want to watch?
(Amy:)Whatever happened
to that ape movie you were in?
(Penny:)Oh, God.
(Penny:)Probably nothing.
(Penny:)I think I saw the director
twirling a sign
(Penny:)outside the Verizon store.
(Bernadette:)Search for it.
PENNY:
Wha... no.
No! Why?
'Cause it would be
fun to watch.
(Penny:)It would be humiliating.
(Bernadette:)Well, now we have
two reasons.
(Amy:)They have it.
(Bernadette:)Please,
can we watch it?
(sighs)
Please?
(Penny:)Fine, but I'm telling you--
it's terrible.
(Amy:)Have you even seen it?
No.
(Bernadette:)Well, maybe it turned out
better than you think.
(bike bell rings on TV)
MAN: Bananas,
get your fresh bananas.
(laughing):
It really didn't.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, this is
superfluid helium.
(Leonard:)Put this in
your mouth,
(Leonard:)your tongue will
freeze and break off.
(Sheldon:)Does it smell like blueberries?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)Then we're probably okay.
(Howard:)Hey, your paper
got mentioned
on the Quantum Diaries
physics blog.
(gasps)
Really?